&lt;i&gt;Fasten seatbelt sign ON&lt;/i&gt;
女士們、先生們，
我們的飛機馬上就要著陸
請您再次確認繫好您的安全帶，
謝謝。
Ladies and gentlemen, our
plane will be landing shortly.
Please confirm that your seatbelt
is securely fasten, thank you.
女士們、先生們，
我們已經到達北京首都機場。
您將在三號候機樓升降。
機艙外的溫度：
4 攝氏度 ；39 華氏度
飛機還將滑行一段距離，
請您繫好您的安全帶，
在座位上耐心等候。
直到安全帶指示燈熄滅。
在此期間，請不要打開手機。
下機時，請小心開啟行李箱，
以免行李滑落。
感謝您選乘星空聯盟成員—
中國國際航空公司的航班。
我們期待與您下次旅途再會。
祝您在北京愉快，再見。
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have just landed
at Beijing Capital
International Airport, Terminal 3.
The temperature is 4 degree Centigrade
or 39 degree Fahrenheit
Please remain seated with your
seatbelt fastened
and the luaggages stored
The use of mobile phone
is prohibited
until the seatbelt sign has
been switched off.
And we'd remind you
to your precaution
when opening the
overhead compartment.
Please take all your belongings
with you
when you disembark.
Thank you for flying with
Air China,
a member of Star Alliance.
And we hope you'll enjoy
your stay in Beijing,
thank you and good-bye!